Oh
In this match, I think the one we'll really want to watch
is the player who's gained a reputation
as Japan's number one high school setter, Asumu-Miya.
But I want to remind viewers that we should also keep an eye
on the setter from Karasuno.
Tobio Kageyama from Karasuno High School.
Another promising setter and hopeful for the all-Japan youth team.
This is truly an East-West setter showdown.
Shit! I totally nailed that jump!
I forgot to hit the ball!
What the hell am I doing?
You don't have to get that depressed.
Hinato was just thinking about something other than a set.
I think that might be a first.
Do that during a match again and you'll never see another set.
When you hit a jump, make sure you jump and hit, you butt-brain.
Okay!
Did something click for him yesterday?
When he saw a real tiny giant?
Well, I knew Hinato could do that boom jump,
but I didn't expect his reach to get that much higher so quickly,
or all at once.
This is gonna throw off our teamwork.
Hmm...
Hey!
We'll be right back.
Atsumumiya sets the ball on the first contact.
Then Alan Ojiro smashes it right over the net.
Karasuno High School is completely stopped in their tracks, Phil.
Nice kill, Alan!
Jump, jump, Alan!
Nice kill!
You scared the crap out of me!
And as usual, Inazaki continues to break the volleyball mold.
They're the ultimate challengers.
They're good.
Hey, that Alan's not bad.
I'm better, though.
You think so, Pooh, right?
Sure do.
Of course, a surprise attack is always helpful.
But by doing that right at the start, they're intimidating the other team.
Showing them they don't sweat that this is the championship.
They're showing that they can win.
It's easy to keep a cool head if I'm just watching.
But I would hate to play against them.
They piss me off.
Nice kill!
Right at the whistle?
Sorry!
It was long!
Wow.
He had to change his mind in mid-air.
We may be up against the ultimate challengers, but...
We're all challengers here.
We're all trying to be...
the very best.
Shoujo Hirata moves up and nails the spike!
And that was the famous slide attack
from the first year Magic Dude!
Oh, man.
Let it go, Hinata!
Holy crap.
It always gets you the first time you see it.
Man, I almost crashed into that guy with the spooky face.
I almost fell for Hinata's faint.
Wow!
It was a shot!
It was sick!
Totally sick!
That is called a slide.
You don't see it much in men's volleyball.
Oh, yeah?
Fast enough to destroy our block.
But without sacrificing a millimeter of height...
How freaking cool is that?!
It's so much cooler to see it happen in person, man!
Come on.
Does your brain have to regress five years every time we're playing in a match?
You're a duty head!
Doesn't look like the pressure is getting to them the way it does most teams.
Yeah, I was just thinking that.
Four Eyes is eyeballing us.
You can try to distract me all you want.
Should we change it up, then?
Yeah, let's do it.
The second-place Inter-Hite team is here in full force!
They're all here to take us down!
When it's my turn to serve,
it'll be hundreds of them!
Versus me!
It's so awesome!
They're picking up speed!
That was not a great serve.
This first step, it was perfect!
They're running a quick from there?!
Let's go, Red!
Go, go, Red!
Awesome!
You can tell at a glance.
His movement was very polished.
That rapid and precise first step,
it lets him position himself for the set
while also finding his teammates.
He has more time for everything.
Karatsuno's middle blocker scores,
and then Inari's middle blocker responds!
Gotta love it!
Neither side is backing down!
I know they get eight seconds,
but do they have to use all of them?
Noia!
I was half a step late!
Yeah!
When the ghost's a knock-up!
Do your thing to knock-up!
Go!
Look at that!
Your stud muffin's not bad!
Yeah.
Their number 10 made a very effective decoy fank
to draw them away.
But even without that,
he's got a really good eye for the blockers
and the floor as a whole.
When we were kids,
he used to just smash the ball
as hard as he could.
Uh, yeah.
She's really staring.
Girls got it bad.
I've seen this before.
It's like when a track-and-fielder
gets the crowd to clap in rhythm
before they jump or whatever.
But starting it yourself is one thing.
It's different when the crowd
starts doing it on their own.
They might mean well,
but they might just end up
provoking Karatsuno.
I don't like it.
What, Coach?
That clapping that keeps getting faster.
They were already trying to pressure us,
but this is different.
They're like getting our guys
to subconsciously follow their beat.
I thought we'd only have to worry
about the booing,
but this could turn into even more trouble.
We have to get ourselves on even footing
with a good serve,
or we're not going to get anywhere
against these guys.
as well.
Yes!
Shirazaki High
has already managed
their second service ace of the match.
They just keep pulling ahead, Phil.
a narizaki isn't so much a team of established champions but a well-liked up-and-coming crew
that happens to be on a roll and these guys are along for the ride they're cheering squad
it's almost like they have an extra player with them on the court totally man both on and off the court
they use sound and time to expand inarizaki's territory
whoa the other team's got one hell of a cheering section
so what did we miss guys
inarizaki high has already managed their second service ace of the match they just keep pulling
ahead phil what the heck man inarizaki's taken over the entire arena
listen Natsumu that first serve of yours was not your best work
i can't believe you let the cheers distract you
wow suguru if only you guys had beaten nekama you'd be playing here too
uh yeah i guess so thanks mika
a band that's so cool talk about pressure from the crowd glad i'm not playing against them
taiko drums awesome
ah it's psycho guys
that might be a new way to die at least thank goodness they made it here when they did
oh yeah
psycho you're late sorry we just got a little bit lost on the way
yeah we all know you were just up all night drinking
well i was drinking until about five this morning but we left on time
good save dude oh wow he's fast the players here are something else make it a good one
ideally everyone would be silent when it's time to serve but we can't let the other side take over
the rhythm we don't even have to be loud enough to drown them out or anything
we just want our servers to be able to lock on to a different rhythm than what the inarizaki crowd's
doing let's do this
the other team's cheering squad is really something else and kind of annoying
but our job here isn't to destroy a bunch of yay hoos in a cheering contest
i would just beat all their asses
now we might not even be able to give our boys the push they need
they'll keep going on with or without our help
but as long as we can restore a little balance with these jokers it'll be good enough
suddenly i feel like i can hit the best serve ever
all that provocation from inarizaki and karasuno's number 10 isn't phased in the least
i think i might even see a hint of a smile
what kind of serve is he gonna do a spike serve a chunk floater
oh one of those
got it
a double quick
a really fast one from the side tsukishima's ready to stomp across
it hit his foot the ball never touched the ground
what the hell is that is that even allowed well it's not actually against the rules
but i would say it's probably embarrassing
it's him again
your damn hands
i tried but i missed
that was the perfect spot good job
i must restore my honor
back minus
i was completely convinced that set was going straight to young hinata again
maybe inarizaki was watching him a little too closely as well
but to be honest with you i really can't say i blame anyone
and it looks like karasuno is getting its groove back
i was sure he had jumped up to block hinata but he stopped himself
he lured me away
on purpose
it totally looked like he set the ball to hinata there didn't it
it did
that was a good one
simple decoys
they don't work on reed blockers
but here
after first contact
he sent it up to the center of the court
he angled himself to make it look like he was setting the hinata
then sent it to the right
kageyama doesn't just see everything on the court
he also knows exactly what it looks like to the other team
also
hinata's got a really big court presence for someone so teeny
yes he does
man
that one totally looked like it was headed right for me
stupid kageyama
stupid stupid kageyama
they actually did play second in the inner high
and on top of that they have this overwhelming cheering section
but
maybe we've been thinking of them as a much bigger deal than we've needed to
everything is fine
if we take it one step at a time we can work this out
yep
nice kill pito sheep
jump jump pito sheep
one more time
their dual wielder is serving again
what's that mean?
he gonna use two balls or something?
yeah you wish
it means he can hit a spike serve or a jump floater
basically he can serve either like Asahi or kageyama or like Tadashi
but we won't know what's coming until the moment he hits it
oh nasty
and depending on which one it is
we're gonna want our receivers in different positions
with that serve coming in at over a hundred kilometers per hour
just a single step off could change everything
Atsumumiya can use two different kinds of serves
so then I guess that means we aren't going to know which serve is coming until he actually tosses the ball in the air
there's one way for us to tell them apart
count his steps
as part of his serve routine he always gauges the distance with his steps
when he's going for a jump floater he'll be four steps from the end line
for a spike serve it'll be six steps
that's how you can tell what's coming at you
all you have to do is count
it's as simple as that gentlemen
but you can't see every move he makes before a serve on tv
they don't show all that stuff
so how did you figure this out?
I did a whole lot of research on them
I found game film online
watched some videos my buddies took, everything
Thank you sir!
Next four
A jump floater
BRING IT ON!
You may have figured that part out
but you still have to deal with the ball in the air
Oh boy
right in his face
And another service ace for Inazaki
That's Asumumiya, the master of two incredibly powerful serves
Indeedio, that was a doozy
And you know, a powerful serve can directly influence the play of the entire team
If Karatsuno doesn't break this streak
they're going to be in big trouble
Damn, that serve was wicked good
I'm wicked impressed
All right, guys
We've dealt with brutal serves dozens of times before
Now is not the time to panic
Right!
Okay
Hey, Samu
Yes, Samu
We wouldn't want to miss our best chance to score, would we?
Four steps
Again?
Another jump floater?
No
Yes, Samu
Yes
YES
Asahi
Atsumu
Yes
Asahi
Atzumu
инструмент
Yes
This position
This timing
This position, this timing, this angle...
It's perfection!
Perfection!
The ball, it really did come to me.
Hell yeah, bro!
Whoa, that was almost exactly like...
Freak Quick Attack!
The ball, it really did come to me.
The truth is that I wanted to make it happen.
I don't want to make it happen.
lol
Littleions
You've saved post авото.
Next time, found!